# Maciej Moczała



**CONTACT** 

**Phone:** +48 730 731 740

E-mail:

maciej.moczala@icloud.com

### **FOREIGN LANGUAGES**

English – C1 German – A1

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)

### **ABOUT ME**

I am 18 years old and I am proud to say programming is my passion, since 15 years old I have been doing on order websites. Currently working on a big project for transport management. In spare time coding fun projects and trying to figure out my life.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

05/2019 - now

## Programmer // ATMOS (own startup)

- creating web-applications
- creating APIs
- server maintenance

09/2018 - 05/2019

# Intern // Optimal IT

- designing websites
- helping with computer service

### **EDUCATION**

2017 - now

Technikum Informatyczne im. Władysława Szybińskiego w Cieszynie

I am a student

#### **SKILLSET**

| JavaScript  | 000000  |
|-------------|---------|
| TypeScript  | •••••   |
| Node.js     | 000000  |
| Vue & React | 0000000 |
| CSS & SASS  | •••••   |
| Git         | ••••    |

#### Also:

Wide experience with MongoDB & mongoose, MySQL, writing REST APIs, microservices, gulp, npm & yarn

### **INTERESTS / HOBBIES**

New technologies, board games, skiing.